Guide to the Jerald Brauer Papers 1925-1999
University of Chicago Library
- Series X: Restricted, 1925-1999
  - Subseries 3: Restricted Student and Faculty Materials
    - Correspondence G-H, 1967-1994 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence H, 1957 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence H, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence L-M, 1969-1998 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence M, 1958 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence M, 1958 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence M, 1964 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence P, 1949 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence R, 1980-1982 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence R, 1969-1997 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence R, 1960-1968 (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence R, 1961-1966 (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence R, 1961-1968 (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence R, 1957-1958 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence R, 1968-1991 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence R, 1959-1963 (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence R, 1975-1992 (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence R, 1962-1993 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence R, 1965-1969 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence R, 1970-1990 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence R, 1967-1993 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence R, 1963-1999 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence R, 1984 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence S, 1970-1981 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence T, 1970-1996 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence U-Z, 1969-1997 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952-1994 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1987 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1998 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1996 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1995 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1998 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1997 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1991 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1998 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1995 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1981 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1993 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1994 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1992 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1994 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Faculty, Alderton, 1944-1953 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Faculty, Ames, 1945 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Faculty, Baker, 1939-1947 (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Faculty, Barnett, 1932-1951 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, Becker, 1951-1953 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, Chave, 1943-1961 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Faculty, Chave, 1938-1948 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Faculty, Colwell, 1938-1954 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Faculty, Deems, 1943-1954 (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Faculty, Eastman, 1943-1955 (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Faculty, Edwards, 1940-1954 (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Faculty, Feigin, 1943-1945 (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Faculty, Garrison, 1925-1943 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Faculty, Gilkey, 1938-1947 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - Faculty, Gordh, 1938-1953 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, Graham, 1937-1941 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Faculty, Hartshorne, 1938-1955 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Faculty, Haydon, 1939-1949 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Faculty, Hoffman, 1944-1951 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, Holman, 1940-1968 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, Holman, 1940-1968 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Faculty, Holt, 1925-1942 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Faculty, Hudson, 1944-1949 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Faculty, Hyatt, 1943 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Faculty, Irwin, 1941-1951 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Faculty, Jacobsen, 1948 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Faculty, Kincheloe, 1942-1955 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Faculty, Knox, 1938-1949 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Faculty, Lyttle, 1943-1949 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Faculty, Marcus, 1943-1957 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, Marcus, 1943-1957 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Faculty, McNeil, 1941-1950 (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Faculty, Mead, 1940 (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Faculty, Mullenburg, 1943-1952 (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - Faculty, Neal, 1943-1952 (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - Faculty, Palmer, 1943-1945 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Faculty, Parvis, 1944-1955 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Faculty, Riddle, 1938-1943 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Faculty, Rist, 1943-1944 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, Robbins, 1944-1955 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, Schubert, 1946-1949 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Faculty, Spinka, 1925-1943 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Faculty, Shepherd, 1938-1943 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Faculty, Smith, 1938-1940 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Faculty, Snow, 1943-1944 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Faculty, Sprengling, 1938 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Faculty, Stinespring, 1943-1944 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Faculty, Thomas, 1942-1944 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Faculty, Tushingham, 1948-1951 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Faculty, Wach, 1945-1955 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Faculty, Wilder, 1943-1954 (Box 175, Folder 26)
    - Faculty, Wieman, 1943-1953 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Faculty, Williams, 1943-1954 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Faculty, Wilson, 1939-1945 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Faculty, Wright, 1943-1945 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Faculty, Willoughby, 1946-1955 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Faculty, Willoughby, 1941-1945 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Faculty, Willoughby, 1940-1941 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, Willoughby, 1938-1939 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, Van Holk, 1954-1956 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Lecturers, Baillie, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Lecturers, Frankl, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Lecturers, Jarrett-Kerr, 1956-1957 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Lecturers, Neill, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Lecturers, Niemoller, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Lecturers, Sholem, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Lecturers, Woods, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Lecturers, Wright, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Lecturers, Inquires and Notices, 1955-1957 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - A.M./PhD Committee, Student Petitions, 1956-1957 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Applications, 1948-1952 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Appointments, Temporary, 1942-1943 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - Faculty, Beaver, 1959-1960 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - Bennett, Jerald, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Brauer Contract, 1951-1956 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Student Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Student Correspondence, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - Student Correspondence, n. d. (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - Fellowships, 1956-1960 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Lectureship, Haskell Burrows, 1957-1958 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Meadville Theological, Student Materials, 1947-1955 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Positions, Academic, 1958-1959 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations, 1945-1958 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Theological Fellowship, 1956-1957 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Theological Fellowship, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Religious Education, 1955-1958 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Students, Address List, n. d. (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - Student Placement Information, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - Student Lists, 1957-1958 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Student Exams, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Student Exams, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Students, Inquires, 1958-1959 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Student Letters of Recommendation, 1955-1958 (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Student Progress Sheets, 1951 (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Visiting Professors, Prior to 1960 (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Visiting Professor Nominations, 1964 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Visiting Professors, 1960-1961 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Professors, 1962-1963 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Visiting Professors, 1962-1963 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Visiting Professors, 1963-1964 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Visiting Professors, 1964-1965 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Visiting Professors, 1965-1966 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Visiting Professors, 1966-1967 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Visiting Professors, 1967-1968 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Visiting Professors, 1968-1969 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Conferences, 1960-1965 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Appointments Considered, 1963-1969 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Appointments, Inquiries, 1966-1969 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Appointments, Inquiries, 1966-1969 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Appointments, Inquiries, 1961-1965 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Appointments, Inquiries, 1961-1965 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Doctor of Ministry, Student Records, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Research and Travel Requests, 1967-1968 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Faculty B, 1968-1969 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Faculty E, 1967-1969 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Faculty G, 1967-1969 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Faculty H, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - Faculty K, 1969 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - Faculty L, 1967-1969 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Faculty M, 1968 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Faculty O, 1969 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Faculty P, 1967 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Faculty R, 1969 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Faculty S, 1967-1968 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Faculty W, 1967-1968 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Inter-Seminary Faculty Union, 1959-1968 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Visiting Professors Prior to 1964 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1964-1965 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1970-1971 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1971-1972 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1965-1966 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1966-1967 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1967-1968 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Visiting Lecturers, 1968-1969 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Brauer Appointments, 1963 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Faculty, 1980-1988 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Memos, 1971-1987 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1963-1975 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, 1968-1974 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Faculty, 1966 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Faculty, 1963-1992 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Divinity School, Memos and Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Divinity School, Journal of the History of Religions, 1966-1969 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Divinity School, Ministerial Housing Allowance, 1967 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Student Correspondence, 1957-1981 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Student Correspondence, 1967-1992 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Student Correspondence, 1955 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Student Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Student Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Student Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Student Corrsepondence, 1979-1981 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Student Correspondence, 1970-1993 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Student Correspondence, 1975-1998 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Student Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Student Correspondence, n.d. (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Student Correspondence, 1975-1998 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Student Correspondence, 1970-1996 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 4: Restricted Audio and Visual Materials
    - Mini tapes, n.d. (Box 183)
    - 7" Audio tape, Brauer Speech, "Apostolic Women," n.d. (Box 183)
    - 3" Audio tapes, n.d. (Box 183)
    - Microfilm, n.d. (Box 183)